List QuestionList = [
  {
    "questionno": "1",
    "question": "What is SI unit of electric current? ",
    "answer": "Ampere"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "2",
    "question": "Name the instrument that is used to measure blood pressure",
    "answer": "Sphygmomanometer"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "3",
    "question": "What is the valuse of normal temperature of human body ?",
    "answer": "98.6 f / 37 C"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "4",
    "question": "State the fullform of DNA",
    "answer": "Deoxyribo Nucleic Acid"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "5",
    "question": "What is the study of fungi called ?",
    "answer": "Mycology"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "6",
    "question": "What is the molecular formula of sodium bicarbonate.",
    "answer": "NaHCO3"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "7",
    "question": "How many elements are known till now",
    "answer": "118"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "8",
    "question": "Who invented the mobile phone ?",
    "answer": "Martin Copper"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "9",
    "question": "Which is  the largest natural satellite of solar system ?",
    "answer": "Granymade"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "10",
    "question": "Who is known as father of biology?",
    "answer": "Aristotle"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "11",
    "question": "Which chemical is kept in refrigerator as colling agent ?",
    "answer": "Ammonia (NH3)"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "12",
    "question": "When did Nepal launched its first ever satellite ?",
    "answer": "17th April 2019"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "13",
    "question": "Name the nearest galaxy to the Milkyway galaxy",
    "answer": "Andromeda Galaxy"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "14",
    "question":
        "I am an alloy made by mixing 88% copper and 12% tin, Who am I ?",
    "answer": "Brozen"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "15",
    "question":
        "The longest bone of human body is fermur, Which is the shortset bone of human body?",
    "answer": " Stapes"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "16",
    "question": "What is the main ore of silver ?",
    "answer": "Agrentite / Silver Sulphide"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "17",
    "question": "How many chromosomes are found in dog ?",
    "answer": "78 chromosomes / 39 pairs"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "18",
    "question": "Who was the inventor of thermometer ?",
    "answer": "Galileo Galilei"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "19",
    "question": "Name the instrument that measure atmospheric pressure.",
    "answer": "Barometer / Mercury barome"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "20",
    "question": "Which country landed on Mars first ?",
    "answer": "Soviet Union"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "21",
    "question": "What is fullform of NASA",
    "answer": "National Aeronautics and Space Administration"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "22",
    "question": "Which acid is found in milk ?",
    "answer": "Latic acid"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "23",
    "question": "Which acid is found in apple ?",
    "answer": "Malic acid"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "24",
    "question": "Which gland is responsble for production of insulin hormone ?",
    "answer": "Pancereas"
  },
  {
    "questionno": "25",
    "question": "Which muscle is found only in heart ?",
    "answer": "Cardiac muscle"
  },
];
